{"data":[{"question":"Neither Margaret nor Sheila ________ at home.","a":"was","b":"have","c":"had been","d":"has","answer":"1","explain":"\n- To be at home= stay at home","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"You can ________ eat fish ________ meat. We have both.","a":"neither\/nor","b":"either\/or","c":"both\/nor","d":"either\/nor","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Either\/or: used to begin a list of two or more possibilities","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"She gave me two books for my birthday but I haven't read ________ yet.","a":"neither","b":"nor","c":"either","d":"both","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Not...either = Neither = none of two book","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Did you read the two books?' 'Yes, but ________ interesting.'","a":"neither was","b":"either were","c":"either was","d":"none were","answer":"1","explain":"\nNeither = none of two book","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The room was _______ dark and gloomy.","a":"neither","b":"either","c":"none","d":"both","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Both...and: used to emphasize that something is true not just of one person, thing, or situation but also of another ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"_________ you tell him _________ I do.","a":"Neither\/nor","b":"Either\/nor","c":"Either\/or","d":"Neither\/or","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Either...or: used to say that if one thing does not happen then something else will have to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I found the climate _______ wet and cold.","a":"both of","b":"both","c":"either","d":"neither","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Both...and: used to emphasize that something is true not just of one person, thing, or situation but also of another ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"You two, boys! Can _________ you speak English?","a":"either","b":"either of","c":"neither","d":"boy","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Either of : one or the other ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"We checked the two doors and found _________ them locked.","a":"either","b":"either of","c":"neither","d":"both of","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Both: used to talk about two people, things... together","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"We _______ saw the accident.","a":"both","b":"neither","c":"either","d":"none","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Both: used to talk about two people, things... together","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}